

Muhammad Noman Khan

Looking out for great Opportunities

Profile

A confident, reliable and enthusiastic individual, with previous strong customer service & client relations experience and well acquainted with office coordination, sales executive and office administration. I enjoy helping clients/customers, colleagues and individuals solve the problems that they may have with in the business. I am a great communicator, over the phone, face to face and via email. I am a people person at the core and with my skills I am always face of my organization. Took great pride in ensuring positive overall customer experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TNS Beaconhouse – Digital media & Events Coordinator 2021-2023

- Management of social media
- Day to day post of all events/ activity of school
- Day to day posts on social media of calendar days
- Designing/ Concept of student handbooks, staff handbooks, Admission campaigns
- Management and planning of all events of the campus
- Management of day to day different projects of classes
- Coordination with all departments regarding day to day activities
- Management of student data
- Day to day video post/update on social media from head of school
- Interaction with parents and planning campaigns for charity purposes
- Planning campaigns with parents for financial relief packages for junior staff

Tryangle Productions Media House – Production Manager 2017-2021

- Planning and management of tv commercials with clients
- Visit locations before shooting and make sure of the availability of locations for shoot
- Management of transportation and all equipment for shoot
- Management of client's data
- Finalizing the budget with clients
- Interaction with actors and manage them on shooting
- Interaction with directors and producers for finalizing the locations and budget
- Giving tasks to labor on daily basis to make sure everything is safe and ready to available in warehouse
- Interaction with different companies to keep them in loop for their sponsorship
- Day to day posts on social media of tv commercial videos

Global Bridge Communications – Customer Service Representative 2015-2017

- Inbound USA call center campaign
- Receive customer calls regarding installation of new tv services
- Provide them with best services
- Handling customer queries on the call and give them best response
- Send emails to the customers in daily basis to keep an update
- Call customer for their feedback about the services

CONTACT





khan.tryanale@amail.com

LANGUAGES

Urdu – Native **English** - Fluent

EDUCATION

Superior University 2017

BS Hons in Mass Communication

Punjab College 2012

Intermediate in Commerce

English Grammar School 2010

Matriculation in medical

SKILLS

- Team Leader
- Sales Skills
- Communication skills
- Listening skills
- Self-control
- Positive attitude
- Assertiveness
- Conflict resolution
- Empathy
- Depersonalization
- Time Management
- Adaptability
- Quick learner

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Proficient with Adobe Photoshop series and other photo and video editing software.
- Organized tasks using Google Calendar
- Meetings using Google Calendar, Google meet
- CRM Software
- Beams Software

COURSE WITH CERTIFICATE

- Graphic Designing
- Participation and winning prize in Nikon Photo walk
- Participation in National Nikon Photography Competition
- Business Analysis & Process Management
- Project Management

HOBBIES

Traveling
Swimming
Handcrafts
Cricket
Drawing
Tv shows
Book Reading

AREAS OF PROFESSIONAL INTEREST

- Advertising
- Administration
- Customer Services
- Sales Executive
- Insurance (Claims, Sales)
- Education Management
- Marketing
- Office Coordination
- Events Management

REFERNCE

Reference will be provided on demand